&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：在课程开始时，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: At the outset of the course,
我谈到了语言的三个核心支柱。
I talked about three core pillars of the language.
这三个核心支柱之一对于
And one of those three core pillars that's very critical for
你要了解的是面向对象的系统。
you to understand is the objects oriented system.
对象、this关键字和原型，
The objects, the this keyword and the prototypes,
这些构成了面向对象的系统。
those make up the objects oriented system.
我故意说面向对象而不是面向对象
I'm deliberately saying objects oriented instead of object oriented
因为这不是严格的阶级制度，
because this is not strictly a class system,
有一些类是在它之上分层的。
there is classes that have been layered on top of it.
这是很多人喜欢的选择，但是
And that is an option that many people prefer, but
它本质上不是一个阶级系统。
it is not inherently a class system.
所以我们将从理解这个关键字开始，
So we're gonna start by understanding this keyword,
这是这里的基础部分之一。
which is one of the foundational pieces here.
我们来看看班级系统是怎么做的，
We'll look at what the class system does,
位于JavaScript之上的class关键字。
the class keyword layered on top of JavaScript.
然后我们再回来看看这是什么句法糖分，
And then we'll circle back to understand where that is syntactic sugar on top of,
这实际上是原型系统。
which is actually the prototype system.
然后在我们完全理解JavaScript是如何
And then after we've fully understood how JavaScript's
对象系统已经被用来实现类模式，
objects system has been used to implement the class pattern,
在这个单元的末尾，我将留给你们的是一个关于
what I'm gonna leave you with at the end of this unit is a discussion about
类的继承模式，而不是委托模式。
the inheritance pattern from classes as opposed to the delegation pattern.
我要争辩的是，授权模式是一种更强大的模式
And I'm gonna argue that the delegation pattern is a more powerful pattern
我们基本上没有利用因为我们
that we basically aren't taking advantage of because we're
专注于只用JavaScript的原型做类。
focused on only doing classes with JavaScript's prototypes.
授权模式要强大得多，也广泛得多，
The delegation pattern is much more powerful and much more widespread,
但我们只关注班级，非常短视。
but we sort of focus very myopically only on classes.
这让我们比较了面向对象的面向类的编码风格
And that leads us to a comparison of coding styles where OO is class oriented
在JavaScript中，我提出了一种不同风格的代码，我称之为Oloo，
in JavaScript, and I've come up with a different style of code that I call OLOO,
它代表链接到其他对象的对象。
which stands for objects linked to other objects.